for people like, but here I am from Ukraine, the
для людей вроде а вот я из украины
city of Khmelnitsky, from Russia, from where,
города хмельницкого из россии откуда
good afternoon,
добрый день
tremaine, the city of someone, the capital of Delhi, wi-fi, the
тремейн город кто-то столицы дели wi-fi
capital of villages, and you yourself, who is the
столица деревень а вы сами кто по
nationality of the Russian prince in this film,
национальности русский принц этом фильме
am I Ukrainian, am I Russian, do you have between the
я украинец я русский ли у вас между на
price in this is not  fight yes not this account
цена в этом не бьетесь да не этот счет
glad that we are not we are for all the exact place
рад что мы не мы за всех точном месте то
i.e. you are against the war yes we are for peace in
есть вы против войны да мы за мир во
the world well that is against the war well yes
всем мире ну то есть против войны ну да
I understand I want to finally met people
понял хочу я наконец-то встретил людей
who believe that they did
которые считают что неправильно сделал
it wrong that they started the war congratulations  you
что начал войну поздравляем вас и а
and why, after all, Russia attacked
вот зачем все-таки россия напала на
Ukraine, but
украину а
I think it’s shorter, it didn’t attack Ukraine
я думаю она короче она не нападала на
.  through yours, they get through you
они же через ваш они же через вас
, the
получается
Americans are tricks, they are stupid, it turns out that
американцы хитрости они тупые получается
Russia does not die, the Americans do not have their own,
россия не умирает американцы нет свою
so how would Russia protect its
так ну как бы россия защищают своих
border, but through and where what
границу но через а где какие какие
borders is it in Khersons  which region
границы она в херсонской области а
does not allow you to put your
не дает возможность поставить там свое
American guns there close
американское орудия вблизи
among the Russian borders, you saw on the
среди российских границ вы видели на
map where Kherson how many of the number on the
карте где херсон сколько от числа на
Russian border for a very short time
российской границе очень короткое время
how many kilometers from Kherson to the
сколько сколько километров от херсона до
Russian border that there are 5000
российской границе о том что там 5000
like Moscow to Vladivostok to once again
как москвы до владивостока чтобы еще раз
look from Kherson to the Russian
посмотрите от херсона до российской
border how many regions
границе сколько областей у
it has close to you Estonia Finland
нее близко то вас эстония финляндия
Sweden now they are now attacking them in common
швеция вот они сейчас на то общее на них
and
и нападаете
yes wait, the time will come
да подожди придет время
scary
страшно
well, because let’s put
ну потому что на положим на страны нато
Estonia and Latvia small NATO countries you don’t
эстонии и латвии маленькие вы не
attack the Americans there you  don’t want to
нападаете там на американцы вы не хотите
attack the truth
напасть правда
ukraine is fighting
украина воюет
nato troops the game how many you killed
натовские войска игру сколько вы убили
nato soldiers already well not such
натовских солдат уже ну не такой
information is reliable at least one
информация достоверна хоть одного убили
nato soldier was killed the shelter of the
натовского солдатам укрытие
house nato soldiers yes
дома натовские солдаты да
go nuts and there the generals maybe it’s on so
[__] а там генералы может это на так
that’s who from over the car
вот кого из над атомобиль
maybe
возможно
funny characters
смешные персонажи
she just built maybe  you yourself
она просто строили может вы сами
will tell about your vision, look
расскажете о своем видении смотрите
why for what purpose will you go down to the
почему с какой целью вы спуститесь к
goal arranged a survey your country attacked
цели устроил опрос ваша страна напала на
maybe in the world a secret question in the first place
может в мире секретный вопрос в первые
I better tell me if your goal
мне лучше расскажите ли ваша цель то
is to stay here and maybe you
здесь пребывания и может быть вы мне
tell me your vision in general
расскажите свое видение вообще
imagine it in general such sit there
представить это вообще такой сидите там
against the background of the flag before me  my name is Andriy
на фоне флага до меня звать андрей
Vasilyevich, so I’m from the city of Khmelnitsky,
васильевич так я из города хмельницкий
I’m here in order to collect the opinion of
я тут с целью того чтобы собирать мнение
Russians about the war in Ukraine, so because,
россиян о войне в украине так потому что
for example, your country attacked my
например ваша страна напала на мою
country, I look at who supports who does not
страну я смотрю кто поддерживает кто не
support the war
поддерживает войну
and what results the majority
и какие результаты большинство
support doing what for how long
поддерживают занимаетесь что как долго
you have been doing this  you have been studying for four and a
вы этим занимаетесь уже четыре с
half four and a half months, the
половиной четыре с половиной месяца
results, I see that the population of Russia in
результаты я смотрю что население россии
most of its cases is infected with an
большинством своим случаев заражена
imperial virus of some kind and moral, and
имперским вирусом каким-то и моральным а
why did you take what then, because
почему вы тогда чего взяли потому что
these statistics,
эта статистика
wait
подожди
and give approximately, according to my
да даст примерно вот по моему
approximate estimates, out of
приблизительным таким прикидкам из
ten
десяти вот
people here  with whom I communicate only one
людей с которыми общаюсь только один
clearly against the war and not under
четко против войны и не поддерживают вы
support you support see this home not support you think that russia is doing the right thing defending its borders somewhere in kherson what protects the games here you support this war were not supported it is correct and we do not support lawlessness but we support this border protects russia its watch russia now in Kherson, this is how he wages war and in this support the feat of protecting the borders of God, not only Kherson, but yes, and not only I’m just a station at a distant point so that it’s visually clear, but even if it’s so necessary to get there, and if Hitler got there almost near Moscow, why so it was necessary for Putin so even though he wanted to go no further, but he doesn’t go further, apparently he doesn’t go, he doesn’t go, wait, he doesn’t, he doesn’t go to the heart, you understand how he was walking hearts near Kyiv and that you let him go guys roamed normally shorter beguiled ramzi fry then gt where did you go we need at least not needed and let's let's yes yes yes well, how would everything be  do clear maneuvers and it’s normal, otherwise,
сделать четкие маневры и нормально не то
there’s nothing like that the boys would not
там ничего такого пацаны бы не
experience, Ukraine will remain its own there and
переживает украина останется своей там и
we will return at the border of 91, everything is
мы вернемся на границе 91 года все
fine, you will generally be handsome there’s a
нормально вы вообще будете красавца там
leg almost where do you think you’ll return,
ногу почти как вы думаете куда вернетесь
well, to the border of the state of 91, that
ну до границы состоянии 91 года то есть
is, Donetsk Luhansk  area siding
вот донецкой луганской области сайдинг
market floor is more logical during the collapse of the ussr
рынку этаж логичней при распаде ссср
when it all happened before the
когда это все произошло движение до
collapse of the ussr you think that you
распада ссср вы думаете что вы эти
will leave these territories for yourself in the end yes it’s a
территории себе по итогу оставите ну да
matter of time but well and, accordingly,
вопрос времени но ну и соответственно
modern europe that now exists
современная европа которая сейчас есть
it will come the same thing often real
она придет то же самое нередко реальная
as if the borders are those  the very
как бы границы те же самые
territorial borders that
территориальные границы которые а
Iceland now has for you to write down the answer
исландия сейчас есть вам записать ответ
, we will not have Czechoslovakia, yes, as it was in the
у нас не буду чехословакии да как было в
Soviet Union, we will have either in the
советском союзе у нас будет либо в
Soviet Union,
советском союзе
I may be about some years
я примерно может им какие-то года будут
, and there
так и
will be modern Europe, which I would
будет современная европа которая бы я
now be shorter okay  will take away as no no
сейчас короче ладно заберет как нет нет
no and Ukraine will be the one that was under the
нет а украина будет та которая была при
union
союзе
means everything and the one that was at the moment  t
средства все а та которая была на момент
on August 24, 91, and when
24 августа 91 года а когда была
independence was proclaimed, when it’s
провозглашена независимость когда вот
absolutely true
абсолютно верно
through lan Czechoslovakia, so that is,
через через lan чехословакия так то есть
both Czechs and Slovaks absolutely voluntarily
и чехи и словаки абсолютно добровольно
divided these two countries, they are a little
разделились данных две страны они чуть
later on a stupid wife, well,
позже на глупо жена ну
I, and you are sure of this,
я и в этом вы в этом уверены
well, how am I, well  probably a smart person of the
ну как я ну наверно умный человек
browser communicated with many there with the
обозревателя общались со многими там со
parties in this situation, you are absolutely sure of this, the
сторонами в данной ситуации вы в этом
question is visible and at home it’s just time, of
вопрос зримой и дома просто времени
course, and I have one more question,
безусловно и у меня еще один вопросик
but what do you think that boost Russia,
такой а как вы думаете что boost россии
I think see my personal opinion so I
я думаю смотрите мое личное мнение так я
don’t have any
не есть каким
seer so, but my opinion is that
провидцем так но мое мнение такое что
Russia will continue to disintegrate, yes, that is, all
россия продолжит распад да то есть все
empires in the twentieth century disintegrated the
империи в двадцатом веке распадались
British disintegrated there the Ottoman
британская распадалась там османское
Austro-Hungarian you will give the Russian
австро-венгерские ты дашь российская
empire the first phase of the alignment was after
империя первая фаза расклада было после
17 years Finland Poland suburb of
17 года финляндия польши пригороде
Berlin then the Soviet Union
берлина потом советский союз
consolidated part of these territories in the
консолидировал часть этих территорий
ninety-first  the collapse of this
девяносто первом продолжился распад этой
empire continued so into different states there
империи так на разные государства там
already ab  completely different peoples with different
уже абсолютно разные народы с разные
histories, and
истории и сейчас
now this process continues, that is,
продолжается вот этот процесс то есть
Tatarstan will become free, so the Bashkiria, the
татарстан станет свободным так башкирии
peoples of the Caucasus, and so on, that is, the
народы кавказа и так дальше то есть
process of crushing Russia, it will go
процесс дробления россии он будет идти
on and probably you
дальше и наверно дальний восток вы
can clean up the Far East a little, well, I don’t
можете немножечко приберут ну это уже не
know how people are there  in the Far East, how
знаю как там люди на дальнем востоке как
do they identify themselves and how is China
они себя идентифицируют и как там китае
and would you think that there will be
и понес бы вы так думаете что будет еще
some other alliance from
какой-то альянс из тех
those republics that will move away from Russia, the
но республик который отойдут от россии
alliance of
альянс
Tatarstan and Bashkiria there, I understand that the
татарстана и башкирии там я понимаю что
logic of these historical events of the year, that
логика этих исторических событий года то
is, this monster is an empire
есть этот монстр империя она
then it was falling apart then it was holding on there on the
разваливается тогда она держалась там на
bayonets of the Soviet Union now it
штыках советского союза вот сейчас оно
will continue to fall apart what
продолжится развалится какая
configuration will not be assembled will separately
конфигурация не соберутся будет отдельно
Tatarstan separately Bashkiria will they
татарстан отдельно башкирии ли они
create for themselves some kind of medal Ural
создадут себе какой-то там медаль урал
republic this is already their historical
республика это уже ихний исторический
process, that is, progress in her wait
процесс то есть подвижки у неё подождите
for me back then still  not just down the
у меня еще тогда еще не просто вниз
moving shower, you've already passed,
подвижно душ вы ведь уже проходил вот
for example, the last one  In fact, a
например прошлой неделе проходил спраге
forum of free peoples of Russia was held in Prague, but
форум свободных народов россии а вот
representatives of national and someone
представители национальных и кто-то
wants you think someone wants to get away from
хочет вы думаете кто то хочет уйти от
Russia, yes you think and it’s bad for
россия да вы думаете и плохо живется
me, no one cares about anyone, I mean they
никто мне не до кто нет люди я имею
will accept the republics, then look,
ввиду примут республик то посмотрите
for example, Tatarstan back in 90 you  think
например татарстан еще в 90 вы думаете
well, no, 90 slingshots need to be disassembled not a
ну нет 90 рогатки надо разбирать не
sharp year, Putin will pass in the morning, not
острый год путин утру будет прошел не
just look people have remained
просто смотрите люди остались
national consciousness, there are also peoples of the
национальное сознание есть также народы
Caucasus, some want to be
кавказа некоторые хотят быть
independent,
независимыми
but these peoples are much more than the majority of
но это народы очень больше большинство
republics in general, of course they can,
вообще республик они конечно может могут
maybe I, and strongly want
возможно я причем сильно в эту хочу
to believe in this  they lived autonomously, they
верить чтобы они жили автономов они себе
provided for themselves, but nevertheless, now we
обеспечивали но тем не менее сейчас у
have most of these republics, they
нас большинство этих республиках они
depend,
зависят
that is, the insolvent there is a small
то есть несостоятельный там маленькая
economy, the territory is small, and if they are
экономика территория до маленькие а если
large, for example,
большими например
tests of Bashkiria, yes, they have the resources
тестов башкирии да у них ресурсы
to be autonomous, but
позволяет быть автономным дает но если
if they wanted to do this, they would  probably
бы они хотели это сделать они бы наверно
for a long time then well look not to do
уже давно потом ну смотрите не делать
we must be  in the friendly
должны находимся в дружественных
relations of the
отношений
Russian Federation, going to withdraw
российской федерации направляясь вывести
as well as they say, we were all
также как говорит мы все входили в
part of the Soviet Union, if Estonian
состав советского союза если там эстонии
army there wanted to stand out, they said for a
там армия хотели выделиться ним уже
long time, but there was a repressive
давно сказали но было репрессивная
machine, as soon as the repressive machine
машина как только репрессивная машина
gave a slack, so all these republics and
дала слабинку так все эти республики и
sharply two years and everything was cut off
резко два года и все срезан стал
absolutely something like this for the time being, that is,
абсолютно то такая пока есть то есть
modern Russia rests on the power
современной россии держится на силовом
apparatus, that is, it is, yes, that is, there are
аппарате то есть так и есть да то есть
not even internal kate rallies there,
даже нет внутренних кейта митингов там
political movements of the communist parties, as
политические движения компартий как
soon as this repressive apparatus
только вот этот репрессивный аппарат
gives up all the centrifugal force, I
даст слабинку все центробежная сила я
[ __ ], but
срал а
here they are, for example, for such a long time  they waited
вот они например такие долго долго ждали
and waited for the moment, and for example, they,
и дождались момента и например они
like politics, took such a thing for a long time in a
как бы политика такое дело давно в
certain period at about the same
определенный период примерно одинаково
time and left the squad, and
времени взяли и вышли из состава да и
where will they go, I think
куда они пойдут я его в нато их я думаю
they won’t let him into NATO, and perhaps even if it’s not for that,
не пустят а возможно и пусть не на то
why is the military  example
это военный своей зачем на примере
kitkat but
kitkat а
because it is they in the state
потому что это это они в государстве
that but here is our republic  they are getting
которые но вот нашей республике они все
closer, but they border on you, firstly,
ближе но с вами граничат во первых во
secondly, you don’t even think about the fact that
вторых вы не думайте вообще о том что
there are allies of Russia before there is Belarus before
есть союзники россии до есть беларуси до
Belarus, see Belarus is not an
белоруссия смотрите беларуси не
ally of Russia Belarus friendship between Russia
союзником россии беларуси дружбы россии
and Belarus rests only on the personality of
и беларуси держится только на личности
Lukashenka
лукашенко
as soon as Lukashenka does not become any
как только не станет лукашенко никакой
friendship of Russia  Belarus will not be
дружбы россии беларуси не будет
there, maybe something else, maybe
там может быть ещё что-то бы может
Russia might be there by force, but the
россия там силовым методом может быть но
people of the people of Belarus are not this option
народ народ беларуси не этого варианта
either, and you don’t think that there will be one
тоже и вы не думайте что будет такая
that the
которые вступят
countries of Russia will enter there, Belarus, China, but
страны россии там белоруссия китай но и
this may even be enough,
этого даже достаточно может быть
see China very much  a strong player before
смотрите китай очень сильный игрок до
economically because but let's
экономически потому что но давайте
look at the reality and why
смотреть реальность и для чего
should China join us, that is, if China, on the
китаю вступать нас то есть если у китая
contrary, has friction with Russia
наоборот есть трения с россии
historically and the lands that China has a
исторически и земли которые китая есть
bunch of six months one
куча полгода один
body of water the territory of
водное пространство территорию
Russia and the USSR and the Russian Empire took away from
россия так и ссср и российской империи у
China had territorial
китая забирала имела территориальные
claims
претензии
profitable
выгодно
why
почему
and what is the
а какие
relationship between economic russia and ki  taya
отношения экономические россии и китая
here 2 would be in the trade turnover of china the main
вот 2 бы в товарообороте китая основной
segment is occupied by the eurounion and the usa
сегмент занимает евросоюз и сша
this is this statistic how much in the
это эта статистика сколько в
trade turnover china occupies russia
товарообороте китай занимает россия
normal turnover takes how much there is
нормальные оборот занимают сколько там
one percent 10 percent half nakuya
один процент 10 процентов половине накуя
and
а
not this qualitative definition to give it
не это качественное определение дать его
in the frame me by the way it is interesting yes then
в кадре меня вот кстати интересно да то
but not  the last place buddy
но не последнее место дружище
[music]
[музыка]
2 tell me while still on
2 говори мне пока еще на
these I say the normal place is occupied by
этих говорю нормальное место занимает
this bomb
это бомба
but russia for example so here is a sign
но россия например так вот табличка
let's have
давайте
diagrams to
диаграмм к
that
то
I say that america that europe that al
я говорю что америка что европа что аль
in russia everyone passes through china
в россии все через китай проходят
how much gdp america and  how much is the GDP of russia
сколько ввп америки и сколько ввп россии
and how much is the turnover of
и сколько и товарооборота
america
америка
analytics
аналитики
[music]
[музыка]
it’s not salaries, then business brings you
это не зарплаты-то вас бизнес приносит
it’s not salary
это не зарплата
income income income need income I told him the
доход доход доход нужда доход я ему
West not for salaries then you
запад называл не на зарплаты тогда вам
are paid for performing there according to labor well
платят за исполнение там по трудовому ну
as recently
как недавно
[music]
[музыка]
here  list of largest trading partners
вот список крупнейших торговых партнеров
china so
китай так
united states and european
соединенные штаты и евросоюз япония
union japan hong kong south korea taiwan austria  aly
гонконг южной кореи тайвань австралий
vietnam dice there about russia in 12th place
вьетнам dice там о россия на 12 месте
so the trade turnover of china from 20 to for this for
так товарооборот китая с 20 до на это за
what year i
какой год возьму
will take it 2017 this is five years ago
это 2017 это пять лет назад
10 times less than that, the turnover of the
россии в 10 раз был меньше чем то оборот
states from China now we will find
штатов с китая сейчас мы найдем
23 let's 23 next year
23 давайте 23 это будут следующем году
reports no you don't know this word you
отчеты нет тебе это слово не знакома ты
look at similar forecasts we can all
посмотри подобные прогнозы мы можем всех
girls with whom miss america will trade with europe
девочек с кем будет торговать с европой
taking into account
учетом
why me why I leaning  to the data, he
почему мне почему я опираясь на данные
’s not smart, he
вот не он умный
already objected to me in something so that I
мне уже возразил в чем-нибудь чтобы я
leave what he objected to, you say that
оставил что он возразить вы говорите что
somewhere in 23 fantasies,
где-то в 23 фантазиями занимать
wait a second,
подожди секунду
2023 comes in six months and there’s
2023 наступает через полгода а не
probably a forecast already until 2024
наверняка есть прогноз уже и до 2024
forecast in life forecast in modern
прогноз в жизни прогноз в современной
situations when
ситуации когда
we say such popularity is economic
скажем такая популярность экономическая
no one can seriously be here in
никто серьезно не сможет здесь
because we don’t live alone in
потому что мы же не живем не одни в
oppression, but how much we  we live further, further,
гнета а сколько мы же живем дальше
further than
дальше дальше
last year,
прошлого года за 2
2, two months before the invasion of Russia in
за два месяца до вторжения россии в
Ukraine, on a full-scale, someone
украине полномасштабно кто-то что-то
predicted something like this, but
прогнозировал так но
he and but they will gas some
него и но у них газировать нибудь бизнес
business, we have and the levers given there
будет у нас есть а приведенный там
are you here, what Europe has, what
рычаги вы здесь что у европу что у
Russia has  up to what in america
россии до что в америке
well if the steps of the impact of the distance we
ну если шаги воздействия дистанции у нас
have answers what answers
есть ответы какие ответы
do you know what are what on voice acting
вы знаете какие такие какие на озвучке
if not but where i can’t
если не есть но где я не могу об этом
talk about
говорить
it it’s something super-secret that
это что-то такое супер-секретное что
only you know if you now
знаете только вы если вы сейчас
tell it  everything will be kapets on the
расскажите это будет все капец на
federal channels they
федеральных каналах там
say you have a gas crisis there now
говорят у вас там сейчас газовый кризис
you have problems with fuel I’m talking about
у вас с проблемы с топливом я говорю про
Europe it was created the moment the crisis
европу она создана момент кризис
was mind Ukrainian [ __ ] chat time
было разум украинская [__] время чату
from the battle became barely itself was not
из битвы стало еле-еле была сама не
very good but one thing was left fat in
очень но одно одно осталось сало в
chocolate,
шоколаде
let's go by country for 22 years or 21,
давайте мы по странам 22 год еще или 21
although it
хотя на спину
makes no sense to look for 22 on the back, it wasn’t
1 смысла нет искать за 22 еще не было
yet that tomorrow it’s the twenty-first
того чтоб завтра идет двадцать первом
year, everything was very strongly predicted it
году было все очень сильно прогнозировал
would sell the century  and it was all warm up
продаст века это было все прогреть
predictable and already it all was already
прогнозируемая и уже это все было уже
gone through look for already level 20 to
прошло через искать уже 20 уровня
tell 23
рассказать 23
so look we can analyze a
так посмотрите мы от можем анализировать
clear fact how much it was 20 21 then they
четкие факт сколько было 20 21 то они
guess how much it was 23 me really the
угадай сколько было 23 меня правда
truth in days on 21 bet Donetsk
правда во дни на 21 поспорить донецк
why and why  do not be
почему а почему не стоит
afraid of the question, but because in these years, in
бояться вопрос а потому что в эти года в
these years, everything was approximately stable,
эти года примерно было все стабильно
approximately everything was comfortable, everyone lived as
примерно было все удобно все жили как
they lived, well, perhaps something is possible, something
жили ну возможно возможным чё-то чё-то
somewhere no one understood
где то никто не понимал
auch to look at why I say look
auch осмотреть я почему говорю смотреть
at the twenty-third year or  the end of the second
на двадцать третий год или конец второго
year I will let him slacken the end in the middle of the
года дам ему роблять конце в середине 22
year 22, which is now the first weather
года который сейчас идет первый погоде
, the year 22 ends and it doesn’t, and
22 года заканчивается и не и и наступает
such a couple comes
такая вот пара
when it’s not clear where the bangs of the board are, then
когда непонятно где челку доски то вот
if it’s not clear how you want an accurate
если не понятно как вы хотите точный
forecast when to get these about then
прогноз когда получить эти про то и
I say clinker  I also
говорю клинкер был еще
noticed I don’t know because, well, what to
замечу не знаю потому что ну а что чтобы
give out and for the time being mucus that you will
выдавать и пока еще слизи что вы станете
sell to China such new computers
продавать китаю такое новые компьютеры
are a dream of a computer, so you
это мечта компьютера вот так что вы
you start selling China,
начнете продавать китая
well, you’re talking about gaston, so let’s
ну хорошо вот гастон вы про давай так
sell it where the firewood came from, wait, the
продавали его откуда вышло дрова подожди
grain, maybe we will sell the
зерно может быть мы будем продавать
countries that sold our gas, a
страны которые продавалась наши газ
strange game,
странную игру
you can only sell raw materials in this way
вы вы только сырье можете продавать так
and correctly. Basically, you are interested in our
и правильно основном вас интересует наша
territory because of what if  cho us and
территория из-за скорей а если чо нас и
this is not a base
такого не базой
seriously, but look from the hole, I’ll look for you for the time being, I’m
серьезно а вот смотрите и от ямку я пока
also not interested,
поищу вам задам тоже не интересно просто
I just usually ask how it happens
я обычно спрашивают как так получается
that, for example, to live from the Czech Republic, which
что например жить и из чехии которая
lives without oil gas and buys them from
живет без газа нефти и покупает их у
Russia, pays money to Russia, lives better
россии платит россии деньги живет лучше
than  a resident of Russia
чем житель россии
to give
давать
their resources no matter how
свои ресурсы как бы
they date they date their people
не датируют они датируют своих людей
they understand and they don’t have any gas
понимают и на дотации у них нет ни газа
oil all of Europe buys from Russia
нефти вся европа покупает у россии гать
to get them from where to get money to block theirs from where it is
их откуда получать деньги для
such a
блокирования своих откуда такая она
small small country small
маленькая маленькая страна маленькая
Europe the population is larger than in Russia
европе население больше чем в россии
it is  everything taken, but oh well,
это все взятой ну да ладно а ресурсам
but there are fewer resources, but that is, only you have 32 gold
зато то есть только у вас 32 золото
diamonds oil gas is higher than all  Europe is pumped with gas
алмаза нефть газ выше всю европу газом
so we are a little bit into Norway's
накачиваете так мы чуть-чуть норвегии
bills if it turns out you sell so much
счета если получается вы столько
gas to Europe where do they
продаете европе газа откуда у них
get so much money to pay you and where
столько денег чтоб вам платить и куда
does the money you get from
деваются деньги которые вы получаете от
gas
газа и
go and then look at the high
тогда еще посмотреть высокая в европе
population in Europe throughout it is more than Russia,
населения по всей его больше чем россия
well, let  there will be even more than doctors, well,
ну пусть будет даже больше чем врачи ну
not much
не намного
[music] the
[музыка]
population of the European Union, that is, only those
население евросоюза то есть только тех
countries that are members of the European Union, so without
стран которые входят в евросоюз так без
there on the 2nd of Switzerland, is it 450
там на 2-е швейцарии ли это 450
million people
миллионов человек
1 there of the European Union, so a day it
1 туда евросоюза так в день
turns out three times more than the
получается в три раза больше чем
population
население
.
.
Russian now [ __ ] up will still serve
русский сейчас [__] еще будет подавать
I'm behind cover
я я за укрытием
[laugh]
[смех]
I won't thump anymore
я не буду больше бухать
Russian wants to get you drunk you see you don't
русский хочет вас споить видите не на не
see as an agent yes yes he understood that you
видите как агент да да он понял что вы
earn 50 grand now I'll sing him a
50 штук зарабатываю сейчас его спою
garach sedan
гарачий седан
1 dollar
1 доллар
guys you're driving drunk  but
мужики вы за рулем бухаете но
[laughter]
[смех]
I'm wondering how
мне интересно как
come on then show up and wait the
ну давай тогда появись и подожди
store we go can still turn off the
магазин сходим еще может отключить
window yes if it's not there and the faces are like
окне да если не там и лица типа
yourself then let's go to the store with us
собой тогда пойдем с нами магазин
let's have interesting views let's take the
давайте интересных видов давайте берите
door smart guys question and of course you can
двери умники вопрос и конечно можешь мне
cheat me this fact we can everywhere yes
спиздить это факт можем везде да
yes, how would it remain if
да вот как бы пусть это останется если у
you have a conscience, but according to a conscience, well,
тебя есть совесть но по и совесть ну так
let's already have questions of interest, is this our broadcast being
давайте уже вопросы интересны эфир этот
recorded or not being recorded
наш записывается или нет записывается да
?  we’ll
мы записываем и смотрим так вот этот
shoot this Russian against him later
русский против его потом расстреляем
when we capture Tyumen, but this
когда захватим тюмень а вот этот
Ukrainian is an exercise of elbows eggs, I’m
украинец упражнение of локти яйца я
just him for clean water
просто его на чистую воду
not just because I  I
не просто потому что я его я его
checked it how you
проверял как
record the song it’s recorded exactly you
записываешь песню записано аккурат
put it on from the security service of Ukraine we
одеваешь из службы безопасности украины
hand it over
сдаем
and look at our volunteers they
а у нас смотрите у нас добровольцы нас
took us looking for what we went to
взяли искали что мы выходили в
chat roulette so they recorded all the people
чат-рулетку так записывали всех людей
who are against who for the war with Ukraine who
кто против кто за войну с украиной кто
supports the tones to him we are making
поддерживает тонах ему таки мы делаем
such a base  already, but why then
такую базу уже но зачем вот тогда
maintain support.  released you
поддерживание поддерживать . выпущен вы
look we look at this live and you
смотрите мы смотрим вот этим жить и вас
are found further there from a photo like you
дальше там находят по фотографии как ты
for example indeed register me or
например indeed регистрировать меня или
my friend by faces find
моего друга по лицам находят
I think the face has seen you or should have flashed
думаю лицо видел вас или должен мелькали
everything enough to find and
все достаточно для того что и найти
there is always a special
всегда есть специальное программное
software that has exhibited
обеспечение которое вот выставляли
photos  in contact somewhere else,
фотографии в контакте еще где то так
even if you didn’t exhibit somewhere at the
даже если не выставляли вы где-то на
wedding, yours was under the cut
свадьбе были так ваших под катом
and then they find your
засветилась в и дальше находят там ваши
personal data there, and then the
личные данные находят и дальше
special services are already working,
спецслужбы уже работает
depending on how interesting you are
висимости от того насколько вы интересны
and
и
generally clear mom is very interesting
вообще четким мама очень интересно
how interesting  well, they’ve already said a
насколько интересно ну на говорили уже
lot, they’ve spoken
много на говорили
against or for it, depending on
против или за это смотря
which country’s investigative committee will
следственный комитет какой страны будет
analyze
разбирать
[laughter] the
[смех]
whole whole round ball is for Ukraine
весь весь круглый шарик он за украину
except for 1 time
кроме 1 раз
because everyone understands that who is bad in
потому что все понимают что кто плохой в
this situation who attacked
этой ситуации кто напал на
him who that’s it  only in
него кого вот вот именно это только в
russia no one attacked anyone
россии из никто ни на кого не нападал
you are not afraid you are not afraid to
вы не боитесь вы не боитесь дальше
continue in  t this conversation of
продолжать вот этот разговор
such accounting we’ll talk
такого учета поговорим
about what war is and what is not war this
о чем война что а что нет войны эта
war, but it immediately became scary to get there it’s
война а вот сразу страшно стало доехать
not your husband’s fault your husband is forbidden to tamino and
не виноват муж у вас запрещено тамино и
to call from her why it’s not forbidden it’s
называть из на нее почему не запрещают
launched it’s forbidden there is administrative
запущена запрещено есть административная
responsibility if you call
ответственность если вы будете называть
it a war it will be  this clover and
это войной это будет этом клевера и
only three I’m sure of this, tell me what
тремя только в этом уверен ну-ка скажи
administrative responsibility
ка административную ответственность
is there, what article
какой там статье
is there fiscal slander is there already, even
клевета фискальные есть уже даже
journalists have already been caught for this so if
журналисты уже попадали за это так если
we wait, let’s wait well, let
у нас подожди давай хорошо подожди давай
’s catch the logic, let’s catch it, let’s where it’s
так логику давай поймаем давай где
good if we have a war, then we must
хорошо если у нас война значит должна
be complete furniture not Balinese where
быть полная мебель не балинез где
it is said that the war should be complete
сказано что война должна быть полным
zation
зации
full
полный у
we don’t call anyone at
нас вообще никого не призывает его
all just don’t look again who is
вообще просто не смотрите еще раз кто в
in what the war should look if it weren’t for
к что война должны смотреть если бы на
you that’s how it is in your concept
вы не было вот как что в вашем понятии
complete for everyone  7 collected
полном для всех всех 7 собрали
why the
почему
ad is an ad or that a
объявление рекламу или что призываются
new telegram ad is being called or everyone is
новый телеграма реклама или всех
being taken away no that he commands p
забирают нет то что он команды призывают
well, that is, it turns out everything is a lie, there is
ну то есть получается все ложь есть
someone calling as they demanded from
кого-то призывает по мере потребовал у
us days they are calling the military registration and enlistment office about
нас дни призывают военкомат про потому
because depending on where they are from the prism of technology
что смотря откуда они призму техники у
you have those not now I
вас у вас есть тех не вот во сейчас
’ll take it to the winner
возьму чтобы победителю
with my hands to beat our [ __ ] technology
руками бить у нас техники [__] ебаться
where to  you now what kind of equipment
где вот вы вот сейчас на какую технику
exactly you will sit on now I
конкретно вы сядете сейчас я
myself like to know how to fly an airplane of
сам люблю умеете управлять самолетом
course what
конечно каким
any not 25
любым не 25
their name was easily random
их легко было название случайный
called telwing oh what a lust
называемых тельвинг о это какая похоть
what you won’t create any in appearance
какой не создашь любой по виду
if you are taken now so you can
если вас сейчас взять так что вы сможете
do militarily what  you specifically will
сделать военном плане что вы конкретно
break through any one,
любого пробью
and I don’t even need a machine gun, any
а мне даже автомат не нужен любому
skull
черепушку
doesn’t want
не хотят
his wife to contact you, be afraid of a friend of
его жена с вами связываться бояться друг
your military registration and enlistment office yes no, your window in
вашей военкоматы да нет ваши окне в
your mobilizes
вашем мобилизирует
because we just kill
потому что нашему просто мы поубивать
why you are like that and you need to
почему вас таков и надо вателя до сих
keep the vatel still unnecessary
пор ненужного сохранить
scared you would  snakes came to the island,
напугали вы бы пришли на остров змеиные
they would throw off the plane,
скинули бы самолет
not knives, you get up immediately angry, but you
не ножики встаете сразу злой но не нужно
don’t need to, you don’t need to do that, that is  a war is going on a
этого не нужно делать то есть война идет
war is going on regardless of will double
война идет независимо от воли двойной
no afghanistan there was a war
нет афганистане была война
where there was already a special operation in afghanistan
где в афганистане уже было спецоперацию
but it was not a war that is ten
но это это не война была то есть десять
years no of course it’s good but give me
лет нет конечно хорошо а назовите мне
examples when there were wars
примеры когда были войны
in the forty-first year everything and after
в сорок первом году все и после этого
that after 45 years  the war was one
вот после 45 года войны был одним
special operation, and if it turns out this is
спецоперации а если так получается это
not a war, these are all special operations were the
не война это все спецоперации были
politics of
политику
ukraine you are russia the reason
украины вы россия причина
why you have the usa dated weapons in
почему у вас сша датируют оружие в
women because you are the aggressor you
женщин потому что вы агрессор вы на нас
attacked us all
напали нам все
you calculate after 45 years the warrior was
вы высчитать еще после 45 года воин не
not that all or  special operation
было это всем или спецоперации
was only the first second world
была только первая вторая мировая
tell me what kind of war was it’s good
скажи какая где война была вот хорошо
let’s do it in Afghanistan you were at
давайте так в афганистане было вы на
it and it was like it wasn’t it wasn’t a
него и на было как не было это не была
war 10 years there wasn’t a war it
война 10 лет была не война
was America
была америка
I’m not an expert in America well that is
я не специалист америке ну то есть
where the guys
куда ребята
Andrey I remember I remember  before
памятаю памятаю до